My Mercado.
So, the woman that that
that that
There was a woman.
Yeah?
There was a woman at some point.
And wait, let me see. I had a picture
here.
It's kind of weird. Hang on.
What was it?
Yeah.
So, there was a woman
who put my son in in prison.
And the woman
And the woman that put
my son in prison.
The woman that put my son in prison.
Let's translate. What does it say?
So,
that woman
I'll prove it to you.
This is base reality. This is real.
So, that woman, she she put my son in
prison.
My son, she put my son in prison.
It says, "Cancer-stricken My Mercado was
elected without meeting voters in
person. My Mercado ran her campaign from
her sickbed due to cancer, but surged
into parliament and surpassed her vote
total from the last election.
Now she has returned.
A bit of nuance. Kraft drömte equals
elected by cancer, battling cancer. Brag
at Indefolketinget, stormed into
parliament, strong success. Over gig
sits Dem at all, who succeeded her
previous vote
>> Cancer.
Rat cancer. Rat rat rat rat rat rat rat
cancer.
Rat has cancer. RAT HAS CANCER. RAT HAS
CANCER. SHE'S A RAT.
SHE HAS CANCER.
AND I'M GOD. I'M GOD. I'M GOD. SHE HAS
CANCER. OH MY GOD. What did she do to
Jesus Christ?
My son is Jesus Christ and she has
cancer.
And I'm God.
Thank you, God. Thank you.
We live in it. We live in the reality
that Tim Durley, she has cancer.
She put my son in prison.
Look at her nice short hair.
No, I'm not somebody to like uh I'm not
I'm not going to use pride to say
anything. I'm just saying I told you so,
right? It's like
That's what happens with I'm just I'm
just going to say that's what happens
when somebody
changes the fate of my son and get in
his way. She ended up getting cancer.
It's pretty clear. You could see what
cuz she was a politician, right? So, a
politician
put my son in prison in order to get
herself into
politics. So, she's in politics. You
could see she's a politician.
She She Well,
she lost her hair, and she lost her
breasts, and she lost everything, but
she gained a lot of money, and she has
to work
every day for Tim Dooley.
Make a better life, right?
So, Mega So, but she's my peasant,
and she
has cancer in her body.
It's probably because of how rotten she
is and how she's a traitor and a rat.
But,
hey, what do I know about it? I'm only
God, and I can do whatever the
I
A.
This is People don't get in my [__]
way, do you understand? Do you
understand why they don't get in my way?
It's because Where's Marty B's music?